planmoneytax.com 2019-09-24

# Privacy Policy - PlanMoneyTax

You are here: [Home](https://www.planmoneytax.com/) / Privacy Policy

 **Cookies**

This site uses cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

PlanMoneyTax uses cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Google, as a third party vendor, also uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **Pop Up Ads**

PlanMoneyTax does NOT use pop-up ads on the site. If you are seeing pop-up ads while surfing the site, this is arising because your computer is infected with one or more “scumware” or, more politely, “adware” programs. These are software programs that you have installed on YOUR computer that trigger pop-up ads based on the content of thepage you are viewing.

 **Email Addresses**

PlanMoneyTax does not  sell any email addresses. Thus, by contacting PlanMoneyTax the email address you use will NOT be placed on some sort of spam-list.

 **Information Collected**

So, what information do I collect? Nothing fancy, really. The only information I collect is non-personally identifiable information about how many people visited our site daily, using what search engines, and referred from what site. This information is gathered in a program called Google Analytics, which is the most widely used website analytical software on the web today. None of the information in this software program is personally identifiable.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
